[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 55 Days at Peking, the diplomat from what country was slain by Chinese Boxer rebels, thus starting the siege of Peking?", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Japan", "Great Britain", "United States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While out with Veronica, Ron is asked to perform for the crowd at Tinos Night Club.  What instrument does he play in the comedy movie Anchorman?", "correct_answer": "Jazz Flute", "incorrect_answers": ["Violin", "Upright Bass", "Baritone Guitar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Waters extraordinary physical properties are a result of its chemical structure - it consists of two hydrogen atoms and one oxygen atom bonded in what type of molecule?", "correct_answer": "Polar", "incorrect_answers": ["Diatomic", "Nonpolar", "Covalent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Paul Ehrlich, Otto Diels, and Hans Fischer are known as what?", "correct_answer": "German chemists", "incorrect_answers": ["German physicists", "Austrian biologists", "German biologists"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Major League Harry Doyle is play-by-play man for the Indians. What is his sidekicks first name?", "correct_answer": "Monty", "incorrect_answers": ["Murray", "Matty", "Mikey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Tina Turner leaves Ike Turner in the hotel room after a fight, she runs across a highway to stay at a motel. How much money does Tina tell the clerk she has in her pocket?", "correct_answer": "32 cents", "incorrect_answers": ["50 cents", "$2.50", "$1.00"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Pomeranian female dog should be a little larger than the male.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote Jude the Obscure, The Mayor of Casterbridge, and Far From the Madding Crowd?", "correct_answer": "Thomas Hardy", "incorrect_answers": ["William Shakespeare", "Walter Scott", "Matthew Arnold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who informs Hoover that the guys from Delta missed all the questions on their exam in the movie Animal House?", "correct_answer": "The boys from the Jewish House", "incorrect_answers": ["Neidermeyer and Marmalarde", "The boys from the Omega House", "Dean Wormers secretary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This ABC TV series showed the events in an American History class at the fictional Walt Whitman High School in Los Angeles.", "correct_answer": "Room 222", "incorrect_answers": ["704 Hauser", "Gloria", "Maude"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1997 the Atlanta Braves baseball team started playing its home games at Turner Field. What was Turner Field used for before it was a baseball stadium?", "correct_answer": "Track and Field", "incorrect_answers": ["Lacrosse", "Soccer", "Football"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the original source of the Hearst fortune?", "correct_answer": "Mining", "incorrect_answers": ["Farming", "Newspapers", "Oil"]}]